https://www.outdoornews.com/2012/03/01/outdoor-news-privacy-policy/

Site Staff
OutdoorNews.com is a general audience web site, and does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under 13 years of age.
COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION BY OUTDOOR NEWS INC
OUTDOORNEWS.COM collects personally identifiable information (that is, information such as your full name, email address, mailing address or telephone number) only in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect Personally Identifiable Information from you, it is because you voluntarily submit the information to us in order to participate in activities like sweepstakes, contests, photos, newsletters, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, chats or in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information.
OUTDOORNEWS.COM website may be linked to websites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with an OUTDOOR NEWS logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by OUTDOOR NEWS INC. OUTDOORNEWS.COM website may also carry advertisements from other companies. OUTDOOR NEWS INC is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site or for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you¹ve left an OUTDOORNEWS site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any Personally Identifiable Information they collect from you.
Some of the advertisements that appear on the OUTDOORNEWS.COM website are delivered to you by national internet advertising and application companies such as DoubleClick and AdSense. These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to our site(s), including information about the banner ads they display, any cookie they place on your computer and your IP address. To opt out of information collection by DoubleClick, AdSense or similar technologies, you must contact those companies directly.
OUTDOOR NEWS USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
OUTDOOR NEWS INC will use your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION provided under this Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If OUTDOORNEWS obtains PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy.
OUTDOOR NEWS INC employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. OUTDOOR NEWS INC may share your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses) but they may only use your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to provide OUTDOOR NEWS INC with a specific service and not for any other purpose.
OUTDOOR NEWS INC may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows OUTDOOR NEWS INC to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on our web sites. Your non-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION and click stream data about your activities on our sites may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. These companies will not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purposes. Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with OUTDOOR NEW INC¹s advertisers and business partners.
There may be instances when OUTDOOR NEWS INC may disclose PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of OUTDOOR NEWS INC; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if OUTDOOR NEWS INC sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, OUTDOOR NEWS may transfer your PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION to a third party as part of that transaction.
OUTDOOR NEWS INC PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
OUTDOOR NEWS INC uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, OUTDOOR NEWS INC uses reasonable methods to make sure that PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.
Privacy Policy
Outdoor News
9850 51st Avenue North
Plymouth, MN  55442
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *Comment Name *
Email *
Website
Related Posts
Your Daily Wisconsin Outdoor News Update – December 10, 2020Your Daily Minnesota Outdoor News Update – December 10, 2020Illinois Outdoor News Cuffs & Collars – December 11, 2020
Outdoor News Store
A Year's Subscription starts at
$25
per year
Subscribe/Renew Today!
Give a Gift
Shop our online store for products and gear: Print of the Year, Outdoor News History Book, Outdoor News Clothing and more!
Visit the Store
Most Popular
International angling icon Ron Lindner passes at age 86Tips for tracking deer after the shotHigh winds wreak havoc during opening week of Michigan deer firearms seasonMinnesota deer hunter bags a ... gator?Would you shoot a rare piebald buck in Pennsylvania?
Close
Share
Toggle Fullscreen
Zoom in/out
Previous
Next
